Guide to the McCann-Erickson Audiovisual Collection, 1980s-1990s and undated RL.00863
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Original Videotapes, 1980s-1990s, 49 boxes
  - 730. B-B-Bad to Bone (Detroit Office). Undated. Umatic. TRT: Unknown. (Box 48)
  - 731. Women at Work. 1982. Umatic. TRT: 60:00 (Box 48)
  - 732. Women at Work with Barry Day. 1982. Umatic. TRT: Unknown. (Box 48)
  - 733. Women at Work Short Version (San Francisco Version, Copy 8). Undated. Umatic. TRT: Unknown. (Box 48, Video-cassette RL00863-UM-0009, Digital-materials RL00863-SET-0001)
    - Women's Lib: Sex Change (Spain) (Box 48)
    - Montage A: Woman as Sex Object (There is Nothing Like a Dame) (Box 48)
    - Montage B: Mother Drudge (Try a Little Tenderness/Wives and Lovers/No Way to Treat a Lady) (Box 48)
    - Montage C: Women at Work (Hi Ho! It's Off to Work We Go) (Box 48)
    - Montage D: Career Girl (I'm a Star in New York. I'm a Star in L.A.) (Box 48)
    - Metropolitan Life: Editor (USA) (Box 48)
    - Chase Manhattan: Shop Owner (USA) (Box 48)
    - Montage E: Real Jobs (There's Gotta Be Something Better Than This) (Box 48)
    - International Ladies' Garment Workers Union: Sing a Label (USA) (Box 48)
    - Charlie: Bobby Short (USA) (Box 48)
    - Montage F: Self Image (I Am Woman/By Myself/I Enjoy Being a Girl) (Box 48)
    - Enjoli: I'm a Woman (USA) (Box 48)
    - Aviance: Kitchen Striptease (USA) (Box 48)
    - Shell: Panty Hose (Canada) (Box 48)
    - Cadbury: Man About the House (U.K.) (Box 48)
    - Montage G: New Family (That's the Way I Like It) (Box 48)
    - Observer: Marriage (U.K.) (Box 48)
    - Addenda: Karen Daugherty (Japan) (Box 48)
    - Montage H: New Customer (Music Under) (Box 48)
    - Harvey's Bristol Cream: Hattie (USA) (Box 48)
    - Interview sequence (Box 48)
    - Wall Street Journal: T.J. (USA) (Box 48)
    - Polaroid: 1,000 Women (USA) (Box 48)
    - Condom: Surprise (Sweden) (Box 48)
    - Montage K: Reprise (We've Only Just Begun) (Box 48)
  - 734. Barry Day Women at Work Presentation, Venezuela Press Clips. Undated. Umatic. TRT: Unknown. (Box 48)
  - 735. Women at Work 4A's Version (Gone With the Wind). 1981. Umatic. TRT: Unknown. (Box 49)
  - 736. Making Better Advertising 3: Shaping the Creative Idea, Part 1. 1986. Umatic. TRT: Unknown. (Box 49)
  - 737. Making Better Advertising 3: Shaping the Creative Idea, Part 2. Undated. Umatic. TRT: Unknown. (Box 49)
  - 738. Shaping the Creative Idea; Strategy (Short Version). 1984. Umatic. TRT: Unknown. (Box 49)
  - 739. The Gentle Art of Multi-National Advertising (Barry Day). Undated. Umatic. TRT: Unknown. (Box 49)
  - 740. Salted Snacks (These commercials match the TV storyboards in the CAS White Paper on salted snacks.). 1985. Umatic. TRT: Unknown. (Box 49)
- Videotape Documentation, 1970s-1990s, 2 boxes
  Includes content lists removed from videocassette cases and notebooks containing notes on individual videotape contents.
  - Inserts and content lists pulled from reels (Box 50)
    [Information contained therein has been transcribed into this finding aid]
  - Review notebooks for audiovisual collection (Box 51)